<!DOCTYPE webpage SYSTEM "../schema/dtd/website.dtd" [
<!NOTATION XML SYSTEM "xml">
]>

<webpage id="translation">
<config param="desc" value="Software page"/>
<config param="rcsdate" value="$Date: 2005/10/17 18:25:18 $"/>
<head>
	<title>Translation</title>
	<summary>BibleTime translation statistics</summary>
	<keywords>BibleTime, Linux, Software, biblestudy, bible study, KDE, Qt, God, Religion, Bible, devotional, crosswire, sword, translation, webpage</keywords>
</head>

<section><title>Help translate BibleTime into your language</title>
<para>
This is a part of software development where the help of many individuals is needed.
It is our desire to offer BibleTime to users in as many languages as possible.
The following areas are open for your contributions:

<orderedlist numeration="arabic">
	<listitem><para>Translate the www.bibletime.info website.</para></listitem>
	<listitem><para>Translate the program's User Interface.</para></listitem>
	<listitem><para>Translate the Bible Study Howto.</para></listitem>
	<listitem><para>Translate the program's handbook.</para></listitem>
	<listitem><para>Translate the biblical booknames.</para></listitem>
</orderedlist>
</para>

<para>
On this page you can find statistics about the completeness of existing translations for each of these areas, as well
as links to translation templates that you can use to submit new translations which do not yet exist. If a translation
into your language does not yet exist or you want to work on an existing translation, follow these steps:
<orderedlist numeration="arabic">
	<listitem><para>Subscribe to <ulink url="https://lists.sourceforge.net/lists/listinfo/bibletime-translations">the translators' mailing list bibletime-translations at lists.sourceforge.net</ulink>. You will receive information relevant for translators and can communicate with the developers and the other translators. Use this list if you have questions or comments.</para></listitem>
	<listitem><para>Download a template you want to translate or an existing translation you want to enhance.</para></listitem>
	<listitem><para>Use one of the recommended programs mentioned below or some other program and edit the translation.</para></listitem>
	<listitem><para>Send the translation to the translators' mailing list.</para></listitem>
	<listitem><para>Developers will integrate your work as soon as possible. The statistics will be updated after that.</para></listitem>
</orderedlist>
</para>

<para>
For the translation process we recommend that you use the excellent and mature program
<ulink url="http://i18n.kde.org/tools/kbabel/">KBabel</ulink> which works on KDE. It has many advanced features and is a great aid.
<ulink url="http://trolltech.com/products/qt/features/tools/linguist">Qt Linguist</ulink> (part of the cross-platform Qt development package) is adequate for translating the user interface which is in .ts format. <ulink url="http://www.poedit.net/">Poedit</ulink> is a cross-platform .po file editor suitable for our documentation and website translations.
</para>
<para>
A list of the language abbreviations is available at <ulink url="http://www.w3.org/WAI/ER/IG/ert/iso639.htm">www.w3.org/WAI/ER/IG/ert/iso639.htm</ulink>.</para>
</section>


<section><title>Translate the www.bibletime.info website.</title>
<para>
If a translation of the website to your language does not yet exist, you can download and translate
the <ulink url="/po/bibletime_website_template.pot">Webpage translation template</ulink>.
If you want to update an existing translation, use the links in the table below to
download the corresponding file. We usually add the translated pages and the flag at the top if a translation is about 80% complete.
</para>
	<ssi mode="exec" cgi="/postats/website_stats.pl"/>
</section>

<section><title>Translate the program's User Interface.</title>
<para>
If a translation of the User Interface to your language does not yet exist, you can download and translate
the <ulink url="http://bibletime.svn.sourceforge.net/viewvc/*checkout*/bibletime/trunk/bibletime/i18n/messages/messages.ts">
User Interface translation template</ulink>.
If you want to update an existing translation, use the links in the table below to
download the corresponding file.
</para>
<para>
(We are preparing the BibleTime 1.7/2.0 series and have moved to the Qt's .ts file format from the 1.6 series .po format. Due the changes the translations need thorough rewrite.)
</para>
	<ssi mode="exec" cgi="/postats/messages_stats.pl"/>
</section>

<section><title>Translate the Bible study howto.</title>
<para>
If a translation of the Bible study howto to your language does not yet exist, you can download and translate
the <ulink url="http://bibletime.svn.sourceforge.net/viewvc/*checkout*/bibletime/trunk/bibletime/i18n/howto/howto.pot">
howto translation template</ulink>.
If you want to update an existing translation, use the links in the table below to download the corresponding file.
</para>
	<ssi mode="exec" cgi="/postats/howto_stats.pl"/>
</section>



<section><title>Translate the program's handbook.</title>
<para>
If a translation of the handbook to your language does not yet exist, you can download and translate
the <ulink url="http://bibletime.svn.sourceforge.net/viewvc/*checkout*/bibletime/trunk/bibletime/i18n/handbook/handbook.pot">
handbook translation template</ulink>.
If you want to update an existing translation, use the links in the table below to
download the corresponding file.
</para>
	<ssi mode="exec" cgi="/postats/handbook_stats.pl"/>
</section>

<section><title>Translate the biblical booknames.</title>
<para>
Translated Bible book names come from the Sword project. There are no good instructions at the moment but you can find some information and examples by looking at <ulink url="ftp://ftp.crosswire.org/pub/sword/source/sword/locales.d">the locales.d directory</ulink> of the Sword library and using <ulink url="ftp://ftp.crosswire.org/pub/sword/source/sword/doc/translation-template.conf">the template</ulink>.
</para>
</section>


</webpage>
