<!DOCTYPE webpage SYSTEM "../schema/dtd/website.dtd"
[
<!NOTATION XML SYSTEM "xml">
<!ENTITY software_intro_page SYSTEM "software_intro.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY development_join SYSTEM "development_join.xml" NDATA XML>
<!ENTITY translations SYSTEM "translation.xml" NDATA XML>
]>
<webpage id="development_help">
  <config param="desc" value="Help us"
></config>
  <config param="rcsdate" value="$Date: 2008-12-11 22:21:51 +0100 (Do, 11. Dez 2008) $"
></config>
  <head>
    <title
>Hjælp os</title>
    <summary
>Direct and indirect support for the development of
    BibleTime</summary>
    <keywords
>BibleTime, Help us, Help BibleTime, Software</keywords>
  </head>
  <section>
    <title
>Vær venlig at hjælp os ...</title>
    <para
>Our aim is to develop BibleTime into a really mature Bible study application that can by used by everyone. To ahieve this, we need your help. There are different possibilities for supporting the BibleTime project directly and indirectly:</para>
    <section>
      <title
>Ønsker du at bede?</title>
      <para
>At bede er noget alle kan gøre. Hvis du beder for Sword og BibelTimes projekter, hjælper du os lige så meget, som de andre medlemmer af BibleTime-projektets team.</para>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title
>Vil du rapportere en fejl, eller foreslå en ny funktion?</title>
      <para
>You can use <ulink url="https://sourceforge.net/tracker/?group_id=954&amp;atid=100954"
> BibleTime's bug tracker</ulink
> to report problems with BibleTime that you are experiencing. Please be sure to include the version of BibleTime you are using, your Sword version, information about QT/KDE and your operating system, and everything else that is neccessary to reproduce the bug. Before you submit the bug, please query the database to see if a similar bug has already been handled (and is therefore alredy in status "closed").</para>

      <para
>There is also <ulink url="http://sourceforge.net/tracker/?group_id=954&amp;atid=350954"
> a place</ulink
> where you can make suggestions for features you'd like to see in BibleTime. We ask for your understanding that due to our limited time and to our own plans for BibleTime we cannot always comply with all wishes.</para>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title
>Ved du hvordan man programmerer software?</title>
      <para
>Do you know how to program in C++? Are you familiar with the KDE programming interface or are motivated to learn it? If you have time to regularly work on the BibleTime source code we ask you to join our team. If you want to do so, please read the page <olink targetdocent="development_join"
>Join us</olink
>.</para>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title
>Ved du hvordan man skriver dokumentation?</title>
      <para
>Do you think you would be good in working on BibleTime's English documentation? If you think you are, please read the page <olink targetdocent="development_join"
>Join us</olink
>.</para>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title
>Are you good at translating English into another language?</title>
      <para
>BibleTime skal være brugbart for alle. Det er derfor at vi behøver en oversættelse til dit sprog, hvis denne ikke er tilgængelig. Ønsker du at begynde på arbejdet med at oversætte, så kontakt os på info@bibletime.info for at se, om oversættelsen ikke allerede er blevet startet på af et andet medlem at teamet. Vi vil forsyne dig med de filer der skal oversættes.</para>

      <para
>You can find more information about the translation process on the page <olink targetdocent="translations"
>translation</olink
>.</para>
    </section>
  </section>
</webpage>
