<!DOCTYPE webpage SYSTEM "../schema/dtd/website.dtd"
[
<!NOTATION XML SYSTEM "xml">
]>
<webpage id="software_links">
  <config param="desc" value="Link collection"
></config>
  <config param="rcsdate" value="$Date: 2009-02-09 15:10:09 +0100 (Mo, 09. Feb 2009) $"
></config>
  <head>
    <title
>Links</title>
    <summary
>Link collection of good sites</summary>
    <keywords
>BibleTime, Linux, Software, biblestudy, bible study, KDE,
    God, Religion, Bible, devotional, crosswire, sword,
    links</keywords>
  </head>
  <section>
    <title
>List of important Christian pages</title>

    <para
>There are many Christian pages on the world wide web. Here we have collected a list of pages that are important in our opinion.</para>

    <para
>Since we are not the author of the linked pages we are not responsible for their content, we explicitely dissociate ourselves from the content of the linked pages! This is required because German law says you are responsible for the content of the linked pages unless you explicitely dissociate yourself from these pages.</para>
    <section>
      <title
>General Christian pages</title>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.bibletechnologies.net/"
>Bible Technologies Group</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>Hjemmet til det nye tekstudvekslingsformat OSIS, som forhåbentligt vil blive brugt af mange Bibelselskaber og udgivere over hele verden.</para>
      </formalpara>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/"
>CrossWire Bible Society</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>The Crosswire Bible society is one of the few Christian organizations in the world providing everything they make free for all! Crosswire supports the Sword project, the KJV2003 project and many other cool things.</para>
      </formalpara>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title
>Bibelsoftware til Linux</title>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.xiphos.org/"
> Xiphos</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>Xiphos is a Sword frontend using the Gnome toolkit. A really good application. Be sure to check it out!</para>
      </formalpara>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title
>Bibelsoftware til Windows</title>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.bibleworks.com/"
> BibleWorks</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>BibleWorks is one of the best commercial Bible study applications for Windows! Very good but very expensive, too. Very useful for Bible scholars.</para>
      </formalpara>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.bibleworkshop.com/"
> BibleWorkshop</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>The Bible Workshop program is a powerful, commercial Bible study application for Windows, which is available in English, German and French. It is possible to enhance the Bible Workshop using Text libraries you can buy.</para>
      </formalpara>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.e-sword.net//"
>e-Sword</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>e-Sword er et godt og brugervenligt Bibelstudieprogram til Windows systemer.</para>
      </formalpara>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.logos.com/"
>Logos</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>Logos er et af de bedste kommercielle Bibelstudie programmer til Windows. Man kan købe en masse tekster til at udvide det.</para>
      </formalpara>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.onlinebible.org/"
> OnlineBible</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>The Online Bible er et kraftfuldt bibelstudie program til Windows.</para>
      </formalpara>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.crosswire.org/sword/"
>Sword til Windows</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>Dette er et Bibelstudieprogram til Windows lavet af Sword teamet! Sword bliver støttet af The Crosswire Bible Society.</para>
      </formalpara>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.koenigsmuenster.de/rsk/index.shtml"
> Tnach</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>Tnach er et gratis , avanceret softwareværktøj for alle der har noget at gøre med hebraisk og græsk. Det kan blive downloadet gratis mod en donation.</para>
      </formalpara>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.volksbibel.de/"
> Volksbibel</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>Volksbibel 2000.2 is a German, metacard based software Bible study tool for Windows, Linux and Mac. Althouth there are not so many texts as other software packages have, it has some cool things like basic map support included. If you are German try it out!</para>
      </formalpara>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title
>Bibelsoftware til Mac</title>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.macsword.com/"
>MacSword til OS X</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>MacSword er et nyt bibelstudie program til det nye Macintosh OS X system. Skærmbillederne ser meget lovende ud!</para>
      </formalpara>
    </section>
    <section>
      <title
>Udviklingsværktøjer</title>
      <formalpara>
        <title
><ulink url="http://www.sourceforge.net/"
> SourceForge</ulink
>.</title>
        <para
>SourceForge forsørger os med værktøjerne til at udvikle BibleTime med mange team-medlemmer på samme tid! Vi sparer en masse tid og penge ved at bruger deres tjenester.</para>
      </formalpara>
    </section>
  </section>
</webpage>
